[{"id": "5ffb63a45dad637d903c8831", "question": "In England, the victim of an April Fool's joke is sometimes popularly referred to as what?", "answer": "A noodle -- Victims of April Fool's pranks in England may also be called a \"gob\", \"gobby\" or \"noddy\".", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f57", "question": "Abe Vigoda played what well known TV character on the program \"Barny Miller\"?", "answer": "Phil Fish", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe735d0eec85e375820b252", "question": "Who was the architect of Operation Market Garden?", "answer": "General Bernard Montgomery", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59ca3bf744f0f6af5b06662a", "question": "What Canadian professional snooker player is nicknamed \"Champagne Cliff\"?", "answer": "Cliff Thorburn", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7c4d3877e98cb977789a7", "question": "What is the only country with coasts on the Persian Gulf and the Caspian Sea?", "answer": "Iran", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392fd", "question": "In the movie \"The Karate Kid\", what is the name of Daniel's master?", "answer": "Mr. Miyagi", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc82", "question": "Chicago banned the sale of what gourmet food staple in 2006?", "answer": "Foie gras", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5937eaa908d98002fdd633a5", "question": "Which country owns Easter Island?", "answer": "Chile", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b89d", "question": "What do golfers call a putt that is short enough to be conceded?", "answer": "A gimme", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caa0", "question": "Porphyrophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "The color purple", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b610", "question": "A \"Michigan Loader\" is what?", "answer": "Earth moving equipment", "category": "general"}, {"id": "596761082b59efe0e9417ea0", "question": "The fear of some unknown evil is called what?", "answer": "Panphobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe656adae7e414034b5aecf", "question": "Which King of England was faced with the Peasants' Revolt in 1381?", "answer": "Richard II", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133becf", "question": "What was the Paris stock exchange formerly known as?", "answer": "Paris Bourse", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59da1b6af6756c9b30ba14f9", "question": "Which roles does Jamie Lee Curtis play in the film \"Halloween H20: 20 Years Later\"?", "answer": "Keri Tate\u00a0and Laurie Strode", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b571bd067df192a942e336d", "question": "In the book \"Animal Farm\", what is the name of the farm?", "answer": "Manor Farm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c0f", "question": "What is comedian Jon Stewart's full birth name?", "answer": "Jonathan Stuart Leibowitz", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6ac", "question": "How many watts make a kilowatt?", "answer": "1000", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58ab149fbaab681b09292176", "question": "What year did GM first introduce the Corvette?", "answer": "1953", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea3c6eff048f679a45ab3d", "question": "Catagelophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Being ridiculed", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be23", "question": "What color M&M was retired to make way for blue M&Ms in 1995?", "answer": "Tan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5c028d22ea32143fcb1d3b56", "question": "Who wrote the play \"Heartbreak House: A Fantasia in the Russian Manner on English Themes\"?", "answer": "George Bernard Shaw", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397e5", "question": "What were 2 out of 3 of Andrew Lloyd Webbers wives called?", "answer": "Sarah", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be65", "question": "What is the more common name for a \"double-eagle\" on a gold hole?", "answer": "An albatross", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b215", "question": "Who was assassinated by Carl Weiss?", "answer": "Huey Long", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c667", "question": "What is the largest rodent in the US?", "answer": "The Beaver", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd19", "question": "What vegetable is found in dishes served \"Florentine\" style?", "answer": "Spinach", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339451", "question": "Who plays the role of Captain Jack Aubrey in the movie \"Master and Commander\"?", "answer": "Russell Crowe", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af57", "question": "Which country do you associate with the Easter Rising?", "answer": "Ireland", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab54", "question": "What sea does Slovenia have water access to?", "answer": "Adriatic", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe768e8eec85e375820b2a9", "question": "What is the record snowfall in Phoenix, Arizona?", "answer": "One inch", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad31", "question": "Elizabeth Bowes-Lyon was better known by what name?", "answer": "The Queen Mother", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c900", "question": "What is the name for a triangle with 2 equal sides?", "answer": "Isosceles", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d5e", "question": "After his death in a 1998 skiing accident, what famous song title was placed on Sonny Bono's headstone?", "answer": "The Beat Goes On", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc79", "question": "What company's famous plaid pattern is called \"novacheck\"?", "answer": "Burberry's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dee", "question": "What is the name of Porky Pig's girlfriend?", "answer": "Petunia", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b44b", "question": "On August 2, 1876, Jack McCall gunned down which famous lawman?", "answer": "Wild Bill Hickok", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d2c", "question": "What sport is the focus of the movie \"Fat City\"?", "answer": "Boxing", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339747", "question": "What Survivor contestant voted out her own mother in Blood Vs. Water?", "answer": "Ciera Eastin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391c7", "question": "What is the name of Warren Beaty's famous sister?", "answer": "Shirley MacLaine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b622", "question": "What does MW stand for on a radio?", "answer": "Medium wave", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c4d", "question": "What year was Robert Downey Jr.'s first movie, \"Pound\" released in?", "answer": "1970", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133916f", "question": "Who directed the movie \"Reservoir Dogs\"?", "answer": "Quentin Tarantino", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5909cbb7bb53d1af658864d9", "question": "Which artist recorded the Christmas song \"Run Rudolph Run\" in 1958?", "answer": "Chuck Berry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b855", "question": "What suspect in the standard game of Clue has the same name as a bird?", "answer": "Mrs. Peacock", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600f7527a9e54d890926f705", "question": "What U.S. town has a replica of the Eiffel Tower topped with a cowboy hat?", "answer": "Paris, Texas -- Paris, Tennessee and Las Vegas, Nevada also have replicas of the Eiffel Tower, albeit, without the hat.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdaf", "question": "Who did sports fans know as \"the Wizard of Westwood\"?", "answer": "John Wooden", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5971e06089261e916c8e09ab", "question": "What US state was \"Steak 'n Shake\" founded in?", "answer": "Illinois", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e8", "question": "What does M.C. stand for in M.C. Escher's name?", "answer": "Maurits Cornelis", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8b3", "question": "Mimas orbits what planet of the solar system?", "answer": "Saturn", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a852", "question": "Approximately, how many feet above the sea level is Machi Picchu located at?", "answer": "8,000", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "60078c5a0eee65b76b9f2672", "question": "Who became vice president of the U.S. after President Nixon resigned?", "answer": "Nelson Aldrich Rockefeller", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133892a", "question": "In Larry Niven's novel \"Ringworld\", what is the drug that extends human life to near immortality?", "answer": "Boosterspice", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5a4a94a761d1b4d384d5d66f", "question": "What is Queen Latifah's birth name?", "answer": "Dana Elaine Owens", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a44b", "question": "Which river runs through Rome?", "answer": "Tiber", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b571b9e67df192a942e336b", "question": "Who first appeared in the novel \"The Mysterious Affair at Styles\"?", "answer": "Hercule Poirot", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ba7", "question": "What museum, designed by Frank Lloyd Wright, was opened in 1959?", "answer": "Guggenheim Museum", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b752", "question": "Whose ear did Mike Tyson bite in a 1997 fight dubbed \"The Sound and the Fury\"?", "answer": "Evander Holyfield's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a321", "question": "In the 2003 film \"Love Actually\", who played the role of Billy Mack?", "answer": "Bill Nighy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a20", "question": "Who portrayed Michael Corleone's second wife in \"The Godfather\"?", "answer": "Diane Keaton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601b4abb49076251badbeabb", "question": "Where is the oldest African-American theater located in the U.S.?", "answer": "Cleveland, Ohio -- Karamu House opened to the public in 1915. The name is Swahili, meaning \"a place of joyful gathering\".", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bea9", "question": "What is Takeru Kobayashi famous for?", "answer": "Competitive eating", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600f755ea9e54d890926f70a", "question": "In Denmark, what is a Svangerskabsforebyggendemiddel?", "answer": "A condom", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c0c", "question": "What year was Barbra Streisand born in?", "answer": "1942", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5bbd4a5200d154d7af00b8cc", "question": "Which artist founded the record label \"Aftermath Entertainment\"?", "answer": "Dr. Dre", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd6d", "question": "What is the Burmese word for \"Mr.\"?", "answer": "U", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffb5d605dad637d903c8823", "question": "What is the largest city in South America?", "answer": "S\u00e3o Paulo, Brazil", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd9f", "question": "What organization's symbols are the square and compasses?", "answer": "Freemasonry", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338edc", "question": "What famous horse belonged to Gandalf?", "answer": "Shadowfax", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b519", "question": "What religious day follows Halloween?", "answer": "All Saint's Day", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6017373744491cbd7c5a1786", "question": "What is the name of the iron-clad ship that engaged the CSS Virginia during the American Civil War?", "answer": "On March 9, 1862, the CSS Virginia engaged the USS Monitor off Hampton Roads, Virginia in a naval battle that resulted in a draw.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea3d12ff048f679a45ab47", "question": "What are the tiny air sacs in the lungs called?", "answer": "Alveoli", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd2d66e2596a59cbdfbd3aa", "question": "What organization unveiled the largest machine on Earth in 2008?", "answer": "CERN", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5904a077cf93664eb10486b8", "question": "Which brotherly duo created the comic book series \"Ultra\"?", "answer": "The Luna Brothers", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b570", "question": "What event led to the creation of the Superfund?", "answer": "The Three Mile Island incident", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e1d", "question": "What Grimm's fairy-tale character is named for a vegetable craved by her pregnant mother?", "answer": "Rapunzel", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5a9e955a7ccba3ffe45786df", "question": "Malagasy is the native language of which African country?", "answer": "Madagascar", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6013709c1381754895396383", "question": "Actor Earl Hindman always hid behind a fence in which '90s TV show?", "answer": "\"Home Improvement\", which aired from 1991 to 1999.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1f5", "question": "What size engine did the first Volkswagen Golf GTI model have?", "answer": "1.6 L", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59ded115ea2747c8aff16d2f", "question": "What is Thalassophobia the fear of?", "answer": "The Sea or sea travel", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0d0", "question": "Who opened the first \"cinema\" in Paris in 1895?", "answer": "The Lumiere Brothers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59ae9420574a5ce6b56b8243", "question": "What US state is \"The Gopher State\"?", "answer": "Minnesota", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af9a", "question": "Which U.S. President ended his country's participation in the Vietnam War?", "answer": "Richard Nixon", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd6644ea5bfecdd737e0853", "question": "Who was the highest-paid TV host in 2018?", "answer": "Judge Judy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a276", "question": "What US city is mentioned in the first line of the Bob Seger song \"Turn the Page\"?", "answer": "Omaha", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338933", "question": "What is the name of Beethoven's only opera?", "answer": "Fidelio", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b67c", "question": "In what US state did Leon Leonwood Bean open his first retail store?", "answer": "Maine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc15", "question": "United Nations' headquarters are located in what city?", "answer": "New York City", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b05", "question": "What year was Charles Darwin's work, \"On the Origin of Species\", published?", "answer": "1859", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339419", "question": "What do the letters PJ stand for in PJ Harvey?", "answer": "Polly Jean", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b35b01dd7bf43be5e7ad", "question": "A group of elephants is called what?", "answer": "A parade or memory", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca3d", "question": "Which element appears ninth on the periodic table?", "answer": "Fluorine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aff3", "question": "In 1911, what entrepreneur retired as president of Standard Oil?", "answer": "John Davison Rockefeller", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fdffdce1cf6db9ac4808d0a", "question": "What is the largest city by area in the continental United States?", "answer": "Sitka, Alaska", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4a2", "question": "When were the first Winter Olympic Games held?", "answer": "1924", "category": "history"}, {"id": "592eada3f83302ff91e4647f", "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Nebraska?", "answer": "Lincoln", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c66", "question": "What comic strip cat was created by Otto Messmer and Pat Sullivan in 1919?", "answer": "Felix the Cat", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3f3", "question": "What never works at night and requires a gnomon to tell the time?", "answer": "A sundial", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339acf", "question": "Who plays Adam Sandler's boss in the 2006 film \"Click\"?", "answer": "David Hasselhoff", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7bd", "question": "What is measured in Newtons?", "answer": "Force", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b071", "question": "Which former First Lady co\u00adwrote the Declaration of Human Rights which was adopted by the United Nations?", "answer": "Eleanor Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe4ef6406d333868d34d778", "question": "What kind of grass has been used at Wimbledon since 2002?", "answer": "Ryegrass", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b93e", "question": "What was the only nation to qualify for all 16 soccer World Cups in the 20th century?", "answer": "Brazil", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe4ecb206d333868d34d766", "question": "What is the name of the first pyramid ever built?", "answer": "The pyramid of Djoser, also known as the Step Pyramid", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be22", "question": "In what country was actor Rick Fox born?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e56", "question": "Of what famous family are Pongo and Perdita the parents?", "answer": "The 101 Dalmatians", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d12", "question": "What movie's first sequel featured the subtitle \"Farewell to the Flesh\"?", "answer": "Candyman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a46", "question": "What album was the first to be certified platinum by the RIAA?", "answer": "\"Their Greatest Hits\" by Eagles", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5a162cc3f01ec323f8491732", "question": "Arnold Schwarzenegger played Douglas Quaid in which 1990 film?", "answer": "Total Recall", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5904a446cf93664eb10486c2", "question": "In the comic book series \"Strangers in Paradise\", what item of clothing does Francine struggle to keep on during a high school play?", "answer": "Her toga", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be3f", "question": "What is the first book of the Bible named for a woman?", "answer": "Ruth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399fd", "question": "What legendary rock band had a drummer nicknamed \"Bonzo\"?", "answer": "Led Zeppelin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339695", "question": "Who starred as Achilles in the 2004 movie \"Troy\"?", "answer": "Brad Pitt", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a4a957561d1b4d384d5d67a", "question": "Who, or what, was the \"First Reich\"?", "answer": "The Holy Roman Empire", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5c88e83422f44c2d77a29c46", "question": "Reaching 20,320 feet (6,194 meters) above sea level, Denali is located in what US state?", "answer": " Alaska", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338afe", "question": "Which character killed Richard Cory?", "answer": "Himself", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe4ed3a06d333868d34d76b", "question": "The first TV commercial for a toy aired in 1952 featuring what toy?", "answer": "Mr. Potato Head", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bef7", "question": "What nickname was racing driver James Hunts given?", "answer": "Hunt the Shunt", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5febb0737e83c707845b2104", "question": "Which two gems are different colors of the same mineral?", "answer": "Ruby and sapphire", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca79", "question": "What is the Latin word for the beech tree?", "answer": "Fagus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fefa86a6ce05a3942286ed0", "question": "Who was originally to be cast as Axel Foley in the film \"Beverly Hills Cop\"?", "answer": "Sylvester Stallone", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fec8b57ec223966ae8f883b", "question": "What's the name of the opera that Andy plays when he barricades himself in the Warden's office in \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?", "answer": "\"Canzonetta sull'aria\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b22c", "question": "Where did Al Capone spend the majority of his 1931 sentence for tax evasion?", "answer": "Alcatraz", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aef0", "question": "Which bridge in Scotland collapsed in 1879, causing a train to fall in the river?", "answer": "The Tay bridge", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc13", "question": "What year did designer Manolo Blahnik open his first namesakes store in Hong Kong?", "answer": "1991", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59008dbacf842fa4c4ba96ac", "question": "Whose shrewish wife was named Xantippe?", "answer": "Socrates'", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f74", "question": "Who was the first novelist to present a typed manuscript to his publisher?", "answer": "Mark Twain", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b534", "question": "What's the name of Barbie Doll's boyfriend?", "answer": "Ken", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390ac", "question": "When did author J. D. Salinger die?", "answer": "2010", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b78f", "question": "What is the sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel?", "answer": "666", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a9e96b07ccba3ffe45786f0", "question": "What area in the US translates from the Dutch as \"Marshland\"?", "answer": "Brooklyn", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2cb", "question": "What military legend was nicknamed \"The Little Corporal\"?", "answer": "Napoleon Bonaparte", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd5c", "question": "Which of the four biblical Gospels was written by an ex-tax collector?", "answer": "Matthew", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b84", "question": "What cathedral was the fictional Quasimodo a bell ringer for?", "answer": "Notre Dame", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bba2", "question": "Infantry, Cavalry, and Artillery cards are key to what Parker Brothers game?", "answer": "Risk", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a62c", "question": "What US city is nicknamed \"Emerald City\"?", "answer": "Seattle", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b769", "question": "What martial art was originated in 1882 by Japanese doctor Jigoro Kano?", "answer": "Judo", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9d5", "question": "On which US river is the Grand Coulee Dam?", "answer": "Columbia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dc5", "question": "What double-word song title was a hit single by Santana?", "answer": "Maria Maria", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fefc1316ce05a3942286f10", "question": "In the original television series \"Hawaii Five-O,\" who stared as Detective Steve McGarrett?", "answer": "Jack Lord", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd6a4236c0f9723ab15cb51", "question": "What was the only South American country to send troops to fight in World War II?", "answer": "Brazil", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfbe", "question": "Which writer coined the word \"Cyberspace\"?", "answer": "William Gibson", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c15f", "question": "Fax is short for which word?", "answer": "Facsimile", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58ab15e4baab681b0929217f", "question": "What was the world\u2019s first mass-produced car to feature an all-aluminium body?", "answer": "Honda NSX", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388f7", "question": "Whose treasure is said to be the subject of the \"Treasure Island\" map?", "answer": "Captain Flint's", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2f5", "question": "Who directed the 1966 science fiction film \"Fantastic Voyage\"?", "answer": "Richard Fleischer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1bc", "question": "What Manhattan intersection was America's first transfer circle?", "answer": "Columbus Circle", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd96a9523c87fd04dd15e13", "question": "Larry Page and Sergey Brin founded what company in Menlo Park?", "answer": "Google, Inc.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b66f", "question": "A Murphy bed is also known as a what?", "answer": "Foldaway bed", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae81", "question": "Which US president lived at the Monticello mansion?", "answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015eac4fe83fe1f2a824bf4", "question": "What does the color white represent in the American flag?", "answer": "White symbolizes purity and innocence.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afbb", "question": "Which former US president was a Peanut Farmer?", "answer": "Jimmy Carter", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339222", "question": "As a child, what did Casper the Friendly Ghost die from?", "answer": "Pneumonia", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396a7", "question": "What two actors exchanged faces in the 1997 movie \"Face/Off\"?", "answer": "Nicholas Cage and John Travolta", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa02", "question": "What is the capital of Cameroon?", "answer": "Yaounde", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "601debe96b1208747aa7e9d7", "question": "Which famous entrepreneur is credited with inventing the weekend?", "answer": "Henry Ford", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59c1ce3f7bd84c0ea43ad435", "question": "On which river does the capital of Canada lie?", "answer": "Ottawa River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6015e7d5fe83fe1f2a824bd5", "question": "Which English king died in 1066, leaving no heir to the throne?", "answer": "Edward the Confessor", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395e0", "question": "In The Simpsons who said: \"I got a home remedy that'll put the zowzers back in your trousers.\"?", "answer": "Abe SImpson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cab2", "question": "Karakul, Dorset, Urial, and Jacob are types of what?", "answer": "Sheep", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397b9", "question": "What instrument did Don Henley play as a member of Eagles?", "answer": "Drums", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdc0fed469bb8041d07a069", "question": "Which beer is from the \"land of sky blue waters\"?", "answer": "Hamm's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59008ce9cf842fa4c4ba96a4", "question": "Warsaw is the capital of which European country?", "answer": "Poland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a37a", "question": "What is the capital of Portugal?", "answer": "Lisbon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be9c", "question": "Who washes his hands in Matthew 27:24?", "answer": "Pontius Pilate", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c022", "question": "What year was fashion designer Gianni Versace killed?", "answer": "1997", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffb61c15dad637d903c8830", "question": "Bammy is a traditional Jamaican bread made primarily of what?", "answer": "Cassava flour", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2b1", "question": "What US president returned the US controlled Panama Canal Zone to Panama?", "answer": "Jimmy Carter", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392af", "question": "What pop star's fans are known as \"Claymates\"?", "answer": "Clay Aiken's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c071", "question": "What is the name of the kneeling cushions in churches?", "answer": "Hassock", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339613", "question": "What sport was featured in the 1985 movie \"Vision Quest\"?", "answer": "Wrestling", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a390", "question": "Where in London are the Crown Jewels kept?", "answer": "The Tower of London", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "594d08881a1c922dd1ac64c4", "question": "The \"Buffalo River State Park\" is located in which US state?", "answer": "Minnesota", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e05", "question": "What show debuted on September 7, 1979, with George Grande anchoring?", "answer": "SportsCenter", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa5d", "question": "How was the country of Belize known prior to 1973?", "answer": "British Honduras", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a654", "question": "The shoreline of which US state is broken by Albemarle Sound?", "answer": "North Carolina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ffa3867c73aa70ea0b70ad0", "question": "Which US state gets its name from a made-up word?", "answer": " Idaho (Mining lobbyist George M. Willing told Congress \"Idaho\" was a Native American phrase for \"gem of the mountains\". He made it up.)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338de3", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"muffin\"?", "answer": "German", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b79c", "question": "What color is the central square on a Scrabble board?", "answer": "Pink", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff0b3fce662d71a53650fe7", "question": "Which European town inspired Vincent van Gogh's famous \u201cStarry Night\u201d?", "answer": "Saint-R\u00e9my-de-Provence, France", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe8b1a401dd7bf43be5e793", "question": "What was the original name of the Popsicle?", "answer": "Eppsicles (Eppsicle was named after its creator, Frank Epperson.)", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b916", "question": "What 2 letters in scrabble have the highest point value?", "answer": "Q and Z", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a442", "question": "What is the volcano near Tokyo, Japan called?", "answer": "Mount Fuji", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58dba441874c93a3298b2143", "question": "In what Puccini opera does Scarpia appear?", "answer": "Tosca", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a181", "question": "Peter Perfect drove the Turbo Teriffic in which cartoon?", "answer": "Wacky Races", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a10a", "question": "\"Need You Tonight\" was a hit for which Australian band?", "answer": "INXS", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6012150063c99d48cd169ae5", "question": "Einstein won the 1921 Nobel Prize for Physics for explaining what?", "answer": "Photoelectric effect -- However, that did not stop him from giving a lecture\u00a0on relativity in his acceptance speech.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5c028d0aea32143fcb1d3b55", "question": "In music, what is the term to gradually decrease in volume?", "answer": "Decrescendo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394e9", "question": "What was the name of the law firm featured in the TV series \"The Practice\"?", "answer": "Robert Donnell and Associates", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a4d99c808b8581f80b092b7", "question": "What soccer team won the 2017 FIFA Club World Cup?", "answer": "Real Madrid", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5af984ddaeb0982ee455954c", "question": "How many sisters does Lincoln Loud have on the animated show \"The Loud House\"?", "answer": "10", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa19", "question": "What is the name of the island that separates the two waterfalls at Niagara Falls?", "answer": "Goat Island", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff3c2f64f032c0db195b488", "question": "What charter did a group of English barons force King John to sign in 1215 at Runnymede?", "answer": "Magna Carta", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5a3", "question": "Who was the 1994 Fifa World Cup winner?", "answer": "Brazil", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe8ab2b01dd7bf43be5e764", "question": "What does the term \"contrived patina\" mean?", "answer": "A weathered-looking surface", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b323403bf195a31e15d73a1", "question": "How many players are there in a Netball team?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea7a41ff048f679a45abe9", "question": "Which constellation are the stars Castor and Pollux in?", "answer": "Gemini", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4d8", "question": "Who was said to float like a butterfly and sting like a bee?", "answer": "Muhammad Ali", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad03", "question": "What archaeological site is known as the Lost City of the Incas?", "answer": "Machu Picchu", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c00b", "question": "Rioja wine comes from which country?", "answer": "Spain\u00a0", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beaa", "question": "What cousin of the glockenspiel was named for its ethereal, \"heavenly\" sound?", "answer": "The celesta", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338af6", "question": "Which character killed Albus Dumbledore?", "answer": "Severus Snape", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113389a9", "question": "Who considered founding a utopian art colony at Arles in France prior to his suicide?", "answer": "Vincent van Gogh", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe73812eec85e375820b261", "question": "Which US state has the largest aquifer?", "answer": "Nebraska", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4db", "question": "In what country would you look for the Loch Ness Monster?", "answer": "Scotland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0cc", "question": "What are the names of the twins on the TV show \"Thundercats\"?", "answer": "WilyKit and WilyKat", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58a0f5ea732c90c4fd3069cf", "question": "Who was the childhood playmate of little Jackie Papers?", "answer": "Puff, the Magic Dragon", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff0ae29e662d71a53650fb8", "question": "Which Toni Morrison novel is about a character with the unusual name Milkman Dead III?", "answer": "\"Song of Solomon\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8eb", "question": "What bay is actually the United States' largest tidal estuary?", "answer": "Chesapeake Bay", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b884", "question": "In sports, what does LPGA stand for?", "answer": "Ladies Professional Golf Association", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59ae9363574a5ce6b56b823a", "question": "What was Queen Victoria's first name?", "answer": "Alexandrina", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e5", "question": "What is known as a \"Magnum Opus\"?", "answer": "The greatest, most popular or most renowned achievement of a writer, artist or composer", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b23f", "question": "What royal subject married Rita Hayworth?", "answer": "Aly Khan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c32e", "question": "Most people breathe through one nostril at a time - True or False?", "answer": "True, over 85% of people breather through only one nostril at a time", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339718", "question": "In which decade was Elvis Presley born?", "answer": "1930s", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4ff", "question": "What Poker hand comprises three of a kind and a pair?", "answer": "A full house", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59523c45736d4be723796b36", "question": "What is the name of the highway that travels through all ten Canadian provinces?", "answer": "Trans-Canada Highway, or Route Transcanadienne", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59049d99cf93664eb10486af", "question": "The plane carrying what country\u2019s national rugby team crashed on Friday, October 13, 1972?", "answer": "Uruguay\u2019s", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7bff6877e98cb9777896c", "question": "What is the earliest known walled city?", "answer": "Jericho", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac34", "question": "What is the first word of the text of the US Constitution?", "answer": "We", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a609", "question": "In which European country is the resort town of Spa?", "answer": "Belgium", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5977442d284458f1d785442d", "question": "The original name of New York City was what?", "answer": "New Amsterdam", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "60121a1963c99d48cd169b00", "question": "What kind of nut is used to make marzipan?", "answer": "Almond", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58ab94c586faa38a764be510", "question": "Who bought the rights to manufacture the Isetta in the 1950\u2019s from the Italian company Iso?", "answer": "BMW", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a899dd160d398dc9cf7a6af", "question": "Who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in 1973?", "answer": "Henry Kissinger", "category": "history"}, {"id": "592eaf37f83302ff91e46491", "question": "What does the word \"khaki\" literally translate to in English?", "answer": "Soil-colored", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6000f0ff9a72b906b34e3cff", "question": "Cherry, plum and grape are all varieties of which fruit?", "answer": "Tomato", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5990f4d9fa5fdd6dd25324e7", "question": "Central African Republic shares its western border with which country?", "answer": "Cameroon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "591c3709815febcc896f926c", "question": "What city provided the setting for the 1970's TV show \"One Day at a Time\"?", "answer": "Indianapolis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113389c2", "question": "What Broadway musical was based on the comic strip Little Orphan Annie?", "answer": "Annie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf83", "question": "In ballet, a lowering of the body by bending the knee is called a what?", "answer": "Fondu", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f76", "question": "What was Tom Petty's backing band?", "answer": "The Heartbreakers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6010c7e20775fa611bce67dd", "question": "Why do penny loafers have a slot for a coin?", "answer": "For a payphone -- Penny loafers allowed schoolchildren to always have two pennies if they needed to make an emergency call home.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba5a", "question": "Where did Chicago Bears standout Brian Urlacher play college football?", "answer": "University of New Mexico", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2d9", "question": "Arthur Jefferson better known as who?", "answer": "Stan Laurel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6a12820565ad31a57c7a0", "question": "The Hope diamond was donated to the Smithsonian by what company?", "answer": "Henry Winston", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c291", "question": "How many equal sides are there on a scalene triangle?", "answer": "None", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe73424eec85e375820b22e", "question": "Who succeeded Al Capone after he went to prison?", "answer": "Paul Ricca and Tony Accardo", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffb67445dad637d903c883c", "question": "What country\u2019s land is mostly on an island, although most of its people live on a peninsula across the South China Sea?", "answer": "Malaysia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bab4", "question": "What secret society is the oldest men's club in the world?", "answer": "Freemasons", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ed4", "question": "What SNL cast member voiced \"Waldo\" in Van Halen's \"Hot for Teacher\" video?", "answer": "Phil Hartman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b202", "question": "What three consecutive US presidents were born left-handed?", "answer": "Reagan, Bush, and Clinton", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6db", "question": "What name is given to a ball on a wire that is thrown in an Olympic event?", "answer": "Hammer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ecc", "question": "What baseball player is Santiago's hero in \"The Old Man and the Sea\"?", "answer": "Joe DiMaggio", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ad7e910b24f84e0b9f9ffc8", "question": "What year did Botswana gain its independence from the United Kingdom?", "answer": "1966", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133981f", "question": "All of the clocks in Pulp Fiction are stuck at what time?", "answer": "4:20", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5cd40be1685cf15b733e988c", "question": "Which cartoon family lives in 742 Evergreen Terrace, Springfield, USA?", "answer": "The Simpsons", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bb1", "question": "In 1926, the funeral of what silent movie star attracted a crowd of nearly 100,000 people to view the remains?", "answer": "Rudolph Valentino", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b163", "question": "Who was the 35th president of the United States?", "answer": "John F. Kennedy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd66d87a5bfecdd737e08a2", "question": "What is the most littered item in the U.S.?", "answer": "Cigarette butts", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdd5", "question": "Farnsworth Bentley became famous for holding whose umbrellas?", "answer": "Puff Daddy's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390ea", "question": "Who is the creator of Perry Mason?", "answer": "Erle Stanley Gardner", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b185", "question": "Who succeeded Ronald Reagan as the 41st President of the United States?", "answer": "George H.W. Bush", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5c62b7fa0ae4aacefc17eedf", "question": "Who are the Pines twins in the TV show \"Gravity Falls\"?", "answer": "Dipper and Mabel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecd662ec223966ae8f88d2", "question": "On the TV show \"How I Met Your Mother\", what is Lily\u2019s occupation?", "answer": "Kindergarten Teacher", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395c9", "question": "In The Simpsons, who said: \"I've said it before and I'll say it again: Democracy simply doesn't work.\"?", "answer": "Kent Brockman", "category": "entertainment"}]